This is your end times news update and
can anybody tell me if this is normal
right here? You know, generals from a
foreign nation saluting the president of
the United States. Now, I guess it does
make sense since he is the
self-proclaimed king and if you guys
remember back in the end of April where
he had an interview with the Atlantic
and he declared that he does not just
run the country but the world. I mean,
his name does mean ruler of the world.
Come on. This is exactly how the ruler
of the world would be introduced as if
we were to watch a movie right here. is
exactly how it would go down. I am so
convinced that we are living in an
episode of the Twilight Zone. This is
the best, the greatest Twilight Zone
episode ever. The ratings are going to
be huge, breaking alltime records. And
it sure seems like the king of the
bottomless pit, a bad dawn, is working
overtime right now with all these peace
deals in the Middle East setting the
stage perfectly for the end time
scenario where we can see this right
here. How Mr. A Bad Dawn has a moment to
deliver peace to the Middle East. And
look at the perfect timing that is just
impeccable with this news coming out.
How the new American pope puzzles with
the possible olive branch to a bad dawn
as he boldly pitches himself as the
world's greatest peacemaker. As we can
see right here, Bob emphasized the
importance of global peace on Wednesday
as president. A bad dawn is pitching
himself as a president devoted to peace
in the Middle East. And as we can see,
the new pope is not wasting any time as
he offers to mediate between world
leaders to end wars. Yeah, good luck
with that. Now, since we are on the
topic of peace, we have this news coming
out. How Mr. Donnie is now favored to
win the Nobel Peace Prize. He's such a
good guy. I mean, I'm sure there's
nothing deceitful or nefarious going on
at all. Now, in other news, we have the
beast system infrastructure being built
right in front of our eyes as we can see
that Ripple met with the UAE officials
to discuss digital payment
infrastructure and accelerating
financial innovation. Well, at the same
exact time, we have the $4 trillion
asset manager of JP Morgan Chase
settling first public transaction of
tokenized treasuries. While we had the
false prophet himself in Saudi Arabia
declaring how AI won't just lead to
universal basic income, but universal
high income. Well, at the same exact
time, we can see a soft implementation
of this UBI in New York where we have
this New York governor announces
$400 inflation refund checks for
millions of New Yorkers this fall. Now,
for those new to the channel, this whole
universal basic income is setting the
stage perfectly for the mark of the
beast. You know, where you will not be
able to buy, sell, or trade without the
mark. Hey, let me just clarify how this
is my own personal opinion and
speculation. And also remember how this
video is for entertainment purposes.
Since we're talking about B system
infrastructure, we have this right here.
How Saudi Arabia has approved Starlink
for maritime and aviation use. And
interesting enough with everything going
on over in the Middle East, we had this
6.3 magnitude earthquake that hit Greece
yesterday where apparently this
earthquake was felt throughout that
region as far as Egypt. Now, some other
really big news that not many people are
talking about where I might actually
make a separate video to talk about is
this right here. how the House budget
bill would put a 10-year pause on state
AI regulation where we can see how this
bill would prevent states from enforcing
any law or regulation for AI models.
Now, for those wondering, this is the
bill that Mr. A Bad Dawn was calling a
big beautiful bill where apparently it
says this right here within the bill. No
state or political subdivision thereof
may enforce any law or regulation
regulating artificial intelligent
models, artificial intelligence systems,
or automated decision systems during the
10-year period. Now, for those wondering
why I read it that fast, it's because I
felt it was appropriate to read it as if
it was a side effect list on a
commercial. Interesting enough, with
this bill looming and the possibility of
AI going unchecked and unchained, we had
this right here. How a bad dawn says,
quote, I believe in artificial
intelligence. What a strange thing to
say. A very religious thing to say, I
might add. I'm not sure about you guys,
but while this guy over here is
believing in artificial intelligence,
whatever that means, I'm going to
continue to trust and believe in the
only intelligence worth believing in,
and that is our Lord and Savior Jesus
Christ. With that being said, I want to
encourage you guys to continue to focus
your eyes upon the Lord, trusting in him
every single day. Living by faith and
not by sight, looking unto him,
understanding your identity, that his
blood has cleansed you, has purified
you, sanctified you once and for all.
that you are a child of God sealed for
the day of redemption and to go forth
walking by faith, trusting in him every
single day, understanding that
everything going on right now is
prophecy. It is going to be done and
there's nothing that we can do about it
besides working on our own relationship
with the Lord, growing in maturity,
having our minds renewed and transformed
daily, loving him and loving others,
allowing the fruit of the spirit to come
forth, which is love, joy, peace,
patience, kindness, goodness,
faithfulness, gentleness, and
self-control and just going forth, guys.
Being salt and light in this evil and
wicked, dark world. It is just so crazy
out there. all the division, all the
strife, and we want to be peacemakers.
But the only way that you can be a
peacemaker is understanding your
identity, knowing that you are a child
of God forever. Born of a immortal seed,
born of a incorruptible seed, eternal
life right now, present tense, you have
it. Allow that hope, allow that peace,
allow that joy to just overflow upon you
guys right now. Understanding everything
going on down here is temporary. Do not
get caught up in the schemes of the
devil trying to have you lose your joy
and your hope. Trust in the Lord every
single day, guys. Rest in him. And I
love you guys all so much. God bless.
Remember, the just shall live by faith.